<resources>
    <string name="app_name">[2021]Orbitals LWP &amp; Daydream</string>
    <string name="service_title">[2021]Orbitals</string>

    <string name="pref_about_changelog_text">
        <b>1.4.8</b> (28 March 2016):\n
        <li>Fixed midnight time formatting in 12-hour mode.</li>\n
        \n\n

        <b>1.4.7</b> (27 November 2015):\n
        <li>Implemented user request: new option to rotate the clock in daydream mode.</li>\n
        <li>Fixed weird background colour on dialog buttons.</li>\n
        \n\n

        <b>1.4.6</b> (10 June 2015):\n
        <li>Added support for <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.beatonma.formclockwidget">FORM Clock Widget</a>. The widget can now colour itself based on the colours you have chosen in your Orbitals LWP settings.\n
            - (Requires FORM Clock Widget 1.2.2 or higher)</li>\n
        \n\n
        <b>1.4.5</b> (12 March 2015):\n
        <li>Promoted background images from the \'Experimental\' menu to the \'Appearance\' menu.</li>\n
        <li>New experiment: \'Drip\' style rendering.\n
        - Objects paint their paths to canvas as they move, giving an effect similar to my other LWP &amp; daydream, Drip.</li>\n
        <li>Bug fix: Removed overlapping animation when opening settings app.</li>\n
        \n\n
        <b>1.4.4.1</b> (11 February 2015):\n
        <li>Quick bug fix.</li>\n
        \n\n
        <b>1.4.4</b> (10 February 2015):\n
        <li>Custom background images!\n
            - Currently under \'Experiments\'.\n
            - Ticking the checkbox will open a file picker and then let you crop your chosen image.\n
            - Currently only JPG and PNG files are supported.\n
            - Images are centered on screen. Small images will be scaled up if necessary.\n
            - If you want to choose a new image, untick and re-tick the option.\n
            - This is a temporary arrangement and will be replaced with a nicer setup soon.</li>\n
        <li>Bug fix: Spawning rate is now constant regardless of how many system types are enabled.</li>\n
        <li>Settings menus:\n
            - Bug fix: Settings menu icons no longer invisible after device rotation.\n
            - Bug fix: No more weird double ripples.\n
            - Minor layout and animation tweaks.</li>\n
        \n\n
        <b>1.4.3</b> (03 February 2015):\n
        <li>Minor animation tweaks and an animation-related bug fix.</li>\n
        \n\n
        <b>1.4.2</b> (03 February 2015):\n
        <li>Minor animation tweaks.</li>\n
        <li>Bug fix (sort of): FAB should no longer cover anything in Daydream settings.</li>\n
        <li>Added shadow experiment for Daydreams:\n
            - If enabled, performance will take a major hit!\n
            - Try lowering your object limit for a better frame rate.</li>\n
        \n\n
        <b>1.4.1</b> (26 January 2015):\n
        <li>Split layout for wide devices or landscape use.</li>\n
        \n\n
        <b>1.4.0</b> (23 January 2015):\n
        <li>Fully materialised settings! (For Android 4.2 and greater only - stuff gets prettier as version number increases! Older versions (4.1 and below) still use the old version of the settings.)</li>\n
        <li>Bug fix: trace lines now works properly when \'Show centre of mass\' is enabled.</li>\n
        <li>Better (I think?) colour morphing for collisions and notifications.</li>\n
        <li>I think everything has been tested but this was a big rewrite so please let me know if I broke something!</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.3.2</b> (12 January 2015):\n
        <li>Bug fix: \'Start Daydream\' button should no longer cause a crash on Samsung devices. It still doesn\'t work - Samsung do something different from AOSP - but it should now fail gracefully.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.3.1</b> (10 January 2015):\n
        <li>Bug fix: Stopped pulsing in random colours when no notifications are active.</li>\n
        <li>Finally added streamers to LWP. They have been available in daydreams for ages but I forgot to copy them across!</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.3</b> (09 January 2015):\n
        <li>Added support for an extension app that makes LWP &amp; Daydream objects pulse in different colours when you receive notifications.\n
            - Apps and colours are chosen in extension app.\n
            - Once you have installed the extension, go to the new Notification Pulse settings page and enable it.\n
            - Remember to allow notification access for Orbitals Notification Extension in system settings!</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.2.1</b> (06 January 2015):\n
        <li>Added some more time settings. You can now choose the text colour and size, and choose between filled or outline-only text.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.2</b> (05 January 2015):\n
        <li>Basic material settings theme on Lollipop.</li>\n
        <li>Added option to show current time on Daydream:\n
            - Consider this a beta option for now and please let me know if something doesn\'t look right.\n
            - Choose between 24 and 12 hour formats.\n
            - Displayed time slowly moves up and down a bit to avoid upsetting amoled displays.\n
            - Further options likely to follow.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.1.6</b> (06 October 2014):\n
        <li>Added option to choose a separate colour for object outlines (by request!). Find it at the bottom of the \'Appearance\' menus.</li>\n
        <li>Camera movement when using \'Show centre of mass\' experiment should now be smoother.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.1.5</b> (05 August 2014):\n
        <li>Added particle streamers to Daydreams:\n
            - Shoot a stream of objects in one direction.\n
            - Enable/disable random generation in the \'System generation\' menu.\n
            - Swipe to make your own at will. Length of swipe changes the average speed of objects as they exit the singularity!\n</li>
        <li>Added some more variability to the size of the central object in generated star systems.</li>\n
        <li>Fixed a bug so the target frame rate you choose under \'Performance\' should now be accurate.</li>\n
        <li>You can now access Wallpaper and Daydream settings from your app launcher, under \'Orbitals LWP\'. This was added to enable access to Daydream settings for Android 4.2 users as the normal method doesn\'t appear to work...</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.1.4</b> (14 April 2014):\n
        <li>Fixed a bug preventing chosen background colour being set properly in Daydream mode.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.1.3</b> (25 March 2014):\n
        <li>New \'Bitcrush\' experiment. If enabled, objects will be displayed as low-fidelity approximations.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.1.2</b> (21 March 2014):\n
        <li>Option to change object colours depending on battery charge level. (Currently only implemented for the main LWP - if set, lockscreen colours will obey main settings.)</li>\n
        <li>New \'Experimental\' features menu:\n
            - (Here be dragons! More accurately, here be features that may break.)\n
            - Centre view on the centre of mass.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.1.1</b> (11 February 2014):\n
        <li>Options to toggle daydream interactivity and screen dimming.</li>\n
        <li>If interactivity is enabled you can exit the daydream just by holding your finger down in one spot for half a second - no need to pull up system bars.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.1.0</b> (07 February 2014):\n
        <li>Daydream mode!\n
            - Enable it under Settings > Display > Daydream (requires Android 4.2 Jellybean or above).\n
            - Daydream settings are chosen separately from wallpaper and lockscreen but include all the same options.\n
            - Displays in full screen immersive mode - swipe in from the top or bottom to make your status bar/ navigation bar visible again (requires Android 4.4 Kitkat or above).</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.0.5</b> (06 February 2014):\n
        <li>Multiple object colour options can now be chosen - e.g. you can choose red, orange and yellow instead of just red. (GingerBread devices are still limited to single colours, I\'m afraid.)</li>\n
        <li>Due to the above alteration your colour settings have probably reset to the default \'all\' setting. Apologies for the inconvenience of re-choosing your colours but I hope the ability to choose more than one is worth it.</li>\n
        <li>Minor fixes for pre-Honeycomb Android versions.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.0.4</b> (03 February 2014):\n
        <li>Object size preference.</li>\n
        <li>All colour, size and object style options can now be chosen independently for the main screen and lock screen.</li>\n
        <li>Size and colour option differences melt into one another when the device becomes locked or unlocked.</li>\n
        <li>Re-reorganised options menu.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.0.3</b> (22 January 2014):\n
        <li>Collision options:\n
            - Simple (immediate destruction of smaller object),\n
            - Merge (gradual mass transfer to larger object),\n
            - and None (no collisions, acceleration softened when objects are very close).</li>\n
        <li>Option to change line thickness for wire frames.</li>\n
        <li>Added this changelog-viewing dialog.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.0.2</b> (21 January 2014):\n
        <li>Object transparency options.</li>\n
        <li>Wire frame option to show objects as just their outline.</li>\n
        <li>Lock screen options! You can now choose to change things like colour saturation, brightness or transparency of objects when your device is locked. More are in the works!</li>\n
        <li>Reorganised options menu. Categories now have their own screens as the all-in-one menu was getting a bit long and cumbersome.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.0.1</b> (17 January 2014):\n
        <li>Option to generate softer/desaturated colours</li>\n
        <li>Collisions now gradually transfer mass and size to larger object instead of immediately destroying the smaller object. (This will be an option soon.)</li>\n
        <li>Options to change the strength and direction (antigravity!) of gravity.</li>\n
        <li>Option to choose preferred frame rate.</li>\n
        <li>A couple of small visual tweaks.</li>\n
    \n\n
        <b>1.0</b> (16 January 2014):\n
        <li>First release!</li>\n
</string>

</resources>
